This is meditation number twelve of
number sex, but don't look yet, I
want to explain first.
This is what happens when you learn to
take refuge. This is the drama when you take refuge,
to flee properly.
There are many versions of Bordeaux
Bolanitos, the perfection of wisdom,
and one of them is called "Before the completion of the
election period." Here, 8000 versesman helmet
12,600 1000 mark foreign, and this is
very, very famous, a very famous
quote: "If karma, if you
settle karma correctly, if it
transforms into a physical thing, become
a piano, a cactus." So, if
this karma were to transform into a fresh thing,
then the
universe couldn't hold it. There wouldn't be
enough room in the universe to
accommodate 11. So, the correct
refuge is by going to the
left over from the husband, who does
n't exist.
If you flee into this kind
of protection, not in this area, not
believing in this husband, who
isn't his fault, this chamber  If it were to
finally transform into a singing being,
it couldn't take in this universe.
So what it says is that the great things
that happen to you when you
take refuge correctly, namely the very good
seeds, cannot be measured, not even
by a mother. That cabbage, of
course, is very special, Lord
Butter, among the three high-ranking
objects, among the three jewels,
or as butter, so powerful that if you give
something to the Buddha,
this came. So if you do something for everyone, if you
complete a card dedicated to a
high-ranking person, a
motivation, no matter what,
normally the motivation is 90
percent, but the mother is such a
powerful object that all of this is quite nice.
If you
read this, so to speak, then you will be
rich for several lifetimes, something like that.
Not because of us, but because of them, because
the object is for drivers. We have
already talked about powerful
objects: mom, mom, dad, teachers, emergencies,
people who need something, people who have
helped me, and people who
help other people. If
you take refuge with a good motivation like this,
this chamber can
transform into something other than
making it a brother. So if you  Correct
refuge with the right motivation,
then you take this Kramer, he can't do anything
for others but to
continue, and then tell a
story about it from the left at Ankara,
it's called the Lotus, so it was very
famous, there are several Lotuses, to 2, there's
a short one, into a long one, speaking of
sender, wants to be a vegetarian, so
if you teach the people where it will be taught to
become vegetarians,
a sea Lotus was the book that one
must read,
he makes a long list of all the
meat we know, including
human flesh, and it isn't, so
if you go, Buddhists do
n't accept vegetarians, then they refer to
the Lotus or says to correspond to each other
strongly, to each other
means unhappy, greater one after the other
means very happy person, like America,
the poor knight
[Music]
kills you very strongly at the market, it's not called, doesn't
mean nothing,
if the yoga now we do on the 11th, no, no,
I don't want to die, bunga
affair, happy person, or speaks
to each other,
I tell you, there is a person and
The farmer and his fields have
no stones like those of you who have
recently grown up.
Jesus uses the same language; he
tells the same story. In the
field, there are no more stones,
no tree stumps, and no
thorns, not even a bump, no
pebbles,
and the soil is very fertile, good soil.
If you cultivate the field correctly, if you cultivate it
correctly, if you sow
a fresh seed in it, a seed that
is powerful, and if
you plant it at the right time of year,
and if the seed is not damaged by sun
and wind,
if it is not fried, if it does not
sprout too early,
then the power of these seeds cannot
disappear. If you plant these seeds at the
right time of year in the field,
if you water regularly, and you
also let the soil dry out again
and do not overwater it, and if you
protect this field...
And now Butter speaks to each other: What do
you think? What will you think later? And when
the man who planted the seed then comes to the
field...
And water is perfect, it has
improved, no insects, ore fertilized, and
when the farmer then looks at himself and
this world and he points to the seeds,
my dear farms, please, please don't
wobble, and if you do what that did,
the little leaves and no
fruit,
I don't want wheat, I don't want rice,
I don't need it, please, please don't
grow, didn't understand.
[Music]
Each other, what do you think, do you think then
that because of the farmer's words, the
flames will not turn poor,
I don't think so, that's Amanda, I'm
not allowed to.
[Music]
No, just because the farmer sits down
but forbids the seeds, no
seeds, they won't
grow,
I don't think so. And then he asks, will
these seeds ripen and
produce plants with fruit and
leaves? Is it so that through the words
of the pharmacist, refusing to become rich as a Saxon,
no wheat, that
was his glad it isn't,
that's not the case, although that's how it is, it is
n't, the
farmer's words can  Seeds do
n't stop being
different, not a person who
clings to this life and a person who
believed that this life is beautiful and
wonderful, but if they bring an offering, a
sacrifice to a powerful object,
and if they then say a prayer,
they will often start
or stop, I sacrifice to you, and
I don't want to enter Nirvana,
I don't want to reach it,
I bring you this mistake, but I don't
want to reach it.
[Music]
It's impossible that they wo
n't reach it because they have
sacrificed this tea to a very high object.
Even if they say, "I don't want to reach it,"
they will reach
Nirvana. Nothing can
stop them. There's a
20 percent probability that they wo
n't reach it.
So if you take refuge correctly,
that's because the lotus is so
powerful, the lotus is the basis of entire
religions. For example, in
Japan, they beat the drums and
run around. It's just the first line of the
lotus to carry for millions of
people.  This Sutter
[music]
even if a mother is alone, if a
person doesn't want to be anywhere,
because of this part that they have correctly
taken refuge, they will become
a mother. Nobody can
stop them.
You have, because with the word "mama," because it was, because,
mine, me, with the word "more," or or,
said that, because with the
place, promised. If you only think about the
correct refuge, as a result you will
reach the analysts, and
nobody can stop you.
Nobody can take you away, and Butter said
that, take correct refuge,
or said, so the second husband
story, forget the two jewels, the
second husband, so, take refuge, take this
refuge correctly, and that is the biggest
Kramer that can procure
because then you really understand the
brother, and then I always get
the question: I read the excavator guide,
and in the excavator with grid,
Greek coach Krishna wanted to
be Christa, says commitment doesn't cling to the
fruits of one's deeds. Just don't be like
that, people, but don't expect that
you will have financial success or
a good relationship. Don't think like that.
Just do good things and don't
worry about the result. There are
also those
Americans who do similar things. I don't know
how it is in China, but it's simply said, "Be
good and do it." You don't care what
the result will be. That's
also true for good singers, but you can't stop it.
The result will haunt you.
The money will follow you, the relationships
will haunt you. How good your
health will be? Just be true.
You won't say what the result will be.
You can let that go and say, "
I don't have to get rich.
Not because I want to be rich.
I'm not doing this because I want my husband to be
nice to me. I just want to
be a good person."
You can ask, but you ca
n't stop it.
It will haunt you and catch up with you.
The example here is what I've been doing for
30 years. For 19 years, I was in the
diamond business. For 19 years, I
used my salary to maintain the old
books, and then I did a
couple of years of pulls, and then after that,
after the retreat, I was there once as a...  I
once went with a razor,
a guy I don't know gave me the envelope,
and there was $100,000 Jackson, and
we used it to build me the water
system.
It follows, I just go to a
yoga class and the money just comes,
you can't avoid it.
You can say I don't want this to be
a plant, but the seed will grow.
Meditation number 12 on page 6, what
is the title of the meditation? How hot is
meditation? Even if you
ask that it not grow,
in this meditation you had to
think about karma, using the four
steps so that you remember it as a
habit, so that you achieve the goals
you will reach with the four steps, so
that the animal is desired.
How do you say that it is self-
reinforcing? The
more you use it, the more
you want to use it. You use it. If you
use it once, then plant the karma.
That is, a second time you use it, another time it comes to be. A
third time -
and this very special one, and this is
the very special chamber, that you know
where things come from and it grows, that
this will  So big, but in a positive
sense, like the word of life, refuge,
name that is used together to use the goals
in your life, that it's like
they
multiply themselves exponentially,
so it uses it once and
suddenly half the day and suddenly
the whole day and then even starts to
separate from it,
and it's very, very, very strange,
but money came, same. You can say to me it's
so stupid to always think together, to finally do something
together, but once you
start with it, once
you realize how
cool it is and all these great things that
happen, these supernatural things, what's it
called? You feel happy for no
reason because this kind of thing doesn't just
multiply but
increases exponentially. If you just
try it a few times, then it will
determine your life. Then you can say, I don't want to be
happy, I don't want to have
fun, I don't want to meet new great
people,
I don't want to live in a bubble where
they took me here, a way, most beautiful, like the
cardboard hotel, rented, band, The
Doors, no chance, it's simply great, is
that
So, if you do this meditation,
think about it.
You can't think about it. It's an
expression in English for salvation. So it can
run ahead, but you ca
n't hide. Really find the money. Your
friends will find you.
Success, if I find it. That's a
beautiful meditation. 313, I won't say much about it
now.
Initially, tomorrow evening when we have peace,
I have to.
13, it's gone. It's the typical protection from
the big mistakes in the
past. Protection from the big
mistakes of the past. Most of the
mistakes I made were when I was 16. They were
all in
one year in college. That was the guy
with the umbrella,
number 11. 13. It's similar, the same,
means that
the unpleasant things that will
happen to us in the next few weeks.
This doesn't come from 20 years ago; it
comes from last week. All the
unpleasant experiences will be while
I chase these. What you
experience daily as unpleasant? These unpleasant
things can no longer touch you
if you regularly pay attention. If
you use it, only the four  Using steps will get
you to your goals, but it
also has the side effect that all
chambers are affected.
The things you did last week wo
n't travel.
Yes, we talked about this. Does
anyone in this bubble want to come? When he once
told us, the bandleader is picking
us up,
and they did a program in a neighboring city,
and we always drove proudly.
I have the "
save this life" promise. That's what it's about promising to bring the
country when you
come out of conquering. When there's snow and so on, so
immediate chamber and adaptable,
they can touch you. Who has
or last met before he
shines, the demons.
What are they doing? They also
shot heavy arrows at him because they saw
that he's about to be enlightened.
And when we have to go to the wonder
tree now, we have to take your line
and heavy with us. He will be enlightened.
We would have to take it away from it
and ran to the poetry, and who
shot several arrows and their
spears became and Migros aimed for it,
and the arrows have been in
the  air transformed the flowers and the
blossoms are rained on butter
and then become enlightened. Think about
the problems behind number 13,
maybe legal problems,
tax problems, problems with women, with
a house, in your career.
And if you take refuge, use
refuge to deal with your problems,
and then suddenly it's like
an honor.
They just make off the candy. They don't
touch you anymore, they can't touch you anymore. Would you,
if you did the four
steps, damage the
bad seeds of the past? And
if you think about the four
[music], let's say
I lied to people,
what is the antidote? So,
the third power,
but the third power is the
promise not to do it again, and the
fourth is to do the opposite.
Number three is to
speak negatively, and again here,
to discuss a positive one.
From now on, I will only
tell the truth. I like your dress, the one
you're wearing today. Not the whole
truth, but if you
think about it, it's the same. If you
do the four steps, it's the
same as...  Four forces, it's the
same as what we really have to do with it.
In this, I'll explain the four forces to you,
or just the four steps, explain how to
apply them if you don't make enough money.
Or we'll explain the
steps so you can plant new money.
But the positive effect suits
most people. Then you can use
the positive force instead of feeling
guilty for six weeks that
you've done something bad. Yes, we
teach you the four forces,
but the focus is on the
negative aspect. Are you a bad
person because you were stingy with
others? Secretly admit it, or whatever. No
matter what you have now, share it with
the assumptions.
That wouldn't also be the bad seeds.
Isn't that step number four,
the method that stops the new, very good
seed plants, but at the same time
the old, bad flames?
So it's like killing two fish with one
fly. That's not vegetarian, so
also with wheat. I'd like to
do a meditation with you, and we'll do the
source for that. Then we'll do a
retreat. If I could read the scriptures with you,
then...
Check the chances, phone
90 needs someone, tissue. In the
next life, there could be hordes of glasses,
and then let Nina close her
eyes and not get jetlag.
Relax a mouth, a delicate smile,
exciting eyes, whatever it is, be what
you're thinking right now. You can do it again later;
it's waiting for you. Relax your
shoulders, relax your fingers,
just have fun, enjoy it, and let all
your fears and worries go away. You can take care of them
later. The higher
expenses die.
Make a lady's break
in contact with a teacher. In the
middle of your heart, very deep Wendelin,
a game was into a swimming pool,
from very, very deep into autumn,
and that below meets Werder in a
sugar grain.
It is clear, so big that they both
have room in it, and put it there with him. It is
still inside. Your fights now with
them inside. This sugar comes, that's
quite clear.
Take a moment, two, and come to rest,
and connect with your
teacher.
And now I ask you to
think of the situation in your life that has
scared you the most.  Tell
my story. I was in the reeds, far away
from other people, and I was
bitten by a scorpion. He believed it was
the kind that could kill you,
and one of the pillars of experience in
the imagined for half an hour that
he would die. He thought I was too far away
from other people who could
help me. Then think of a
similar situation, a situation in
your life
that was hopelessly harmless.
I can remember myself, for
example, a small plane, and they
told us that it wouldn't work
and that we might die.
Think of the moment, the saddest, the most
dangerous moment in your life,
the moment when, like that, on the second mast, it
was believed it was impossible.
I tried in such a moment to
remember
the country, the bonds in the country
for these moments. Normally, you are too
afraid to think about it in a moment of
superiority, or there is
no time because the plane crashes.
You have a few minutes after the
scorpion bit your hand, and it
is very, very difficult in such a
moment to think clearly,
to think clearly about the apprenticeship or
through the process of  dying to go
and in the summer in the rider in these
moments just say the name of your
refuge just say lama lama lama the
name of your name or butter if you
can must speak a man that one
of a drama to then then the name of
his lama because of the lame already
brings then make yourself you are so
afraid of everything else
you can the ultimate refuge man
say and sound direction achum john brady from
babies already helps me baby if I am a
if he is the teacher or you
use the name of his teacher to
say the name of your teacher but also
if the plane really crashes
you may not be able to remember that one
earn that, so it is said in the
country just say the name of his
name 22 in this meditation
you practice saying the name of
your lama yourself when you
are in serious danger if you are too two
or too afraid to
remember anything else you just say
the name of German already
and then you come down on the ground with the
name of your lama on your lips
Tradition that in the mind recalls such a
situation, imagine how you get it,
how you repeat the name of your
lama when something
dangerous happens or when you are
dying. Here we spend a
few minutes,
then I concentrate again on your
breath, three long exhalations in contact with
the lama in your heart,
and then bring your grasp back into
this space, and then you could open your eyes, the
tip, what is the name of the migration in
moments of fear and suffering, alone
the words, it is called afterwards in our
line, in the Diamond Mountain lines,
our line,
their song, Piana, we are the new one, pulled off,
we s  And we're good at it, we try not to perform
meaningless new rituals,
going to the temple,
lighting incense, and then we end up in kindergarten
heaven.
We don't encourage people to do such things
because it doesn't help them or
because they don't understand it. But there are
exceptions.
If you truly believe in your heart, if
you have a good, genuine relationship
with your heart teacher, whether it's
a living person, a brother
who lived 1000 years ago, someone
you haven't met yet,
or someone you
can imagine—everyone had that power. The
power of my heart would be
so great that if you just
say its name, if you have extreme
difficulties and hatred—for
example, if you're in the midst of a plane crash just
before you hit the ground, or if
the course has been scorpion-bitten—it
works because of the power of your seed.
The name of my heart would be more
powerful than the name of the brother in
this meditation. Are you experiencing a
car accident, or are you practicing in a plane crash,
or are you seeing  What also
happened this time, I was the
guy who drove too close to me and I was on
fire. The man got angry
and chased me, and then
I drove around the corner and
Vanessa went berserk and shot at me,
and I really felt the powder on
my face and it went through
the windows and I
miscounted.
So if something like that
happens to you, for example, if someone
shoots at you, then say the name of a
lama, and then it's there, and it's good, it's
sufficient,
have that, okay? So we practice this in the three
days.
What do I do if someone
comes at me and shoots me in the head?
Then you should have something handy. Do you remember
Tom KG, his
brother? Someone just
came up to him and totally smashed the house
in my face and
offered their son favors. So in meditation
14, the notes, the ideas, the
emergency kit, press the button, LA
measures.
What is your name? What is my name? What is my name?
You can be so massive  To the
Roma, the meditation 15,
we must stop.
After this meditation, we take a
break.
So we achieve this in the lamb, according to the
advice, but meditation 15,
when I was in Thailand and we all gave refuge vows
and
took refuge, then they all get
totally excited and they show me
new names. I have a new name,
my Filppula, like Diner.
He gave me this very special name.
I am not like you.
You can see it then on TV at Beijing
airport. Suddenly everyone has the
call to the border, even the
businessmen now have the painters
and sand-walkers, and the yoga teachers are doing
it now too, and everyone is on the
wrong side because you can't debate something like that.
It means having taken refuge at that moment.
Then Müller saw they want to use the batteries for
this beautiful little
Dahmer thing. I have pearls and was
deep on it. I have crystal, you still
want. I have gold on my pearls,
but his phenomenal...
I have a refuge name and you  It's
not that
outward appearance, the
external things that are
linked to spirituality, some people wear
religious clothes, the red ones or the
white ones or the black ones, and then they stick to it.
I have a
story, it's uncertain, and there's this
yellow stripe here, and in the monastery
it's very important. If you
hate the yellow stripes here, everyone says, "Kesseler,
Kesseler." I
refused to wear it.
I don't think anyone ever saw me advising that.
I have one, up to small,
it was sewn on the beta, and the
peeps stick to it,
also in tantris development, something very
special. And if you wear it, if
you're not supposed to wear it, then
everyone gets upset about it. What
I like best from the piano line is that
we don't place much value on
these external signs.
I have yellow stripes and you don't have
yellow stripes. But I'm doing well,
and you're not. I like that we, that we, that
we drive ourselves as a person who
has a cosmetic summer in Singapore, and
I think that's very healthy.
We don't have horns.  No high
lamas and the little high lamas and
the big little lamas, we don't have these
things.
[Music]
We don't have any, we don't have anyone who
persecuted us. Don't do it like that,
but you should stick your thumbs in,
but it doesn't change anything. What if you're
not bad? Then you're a bad
person. These are just stupid things. I
'm glad we don't have that. We
work inside, breathed, was to be a
friendly person, and in
meditation, 15, think about it. Do
I cling to these things? That everyone
pulls my mom and pulls the spiritual
person. I try to impress people with
my Tibetan grammar.
The guests, something external, nothing. I remember
how many writings I can't memorize.
How much I've been waiting for him. Can look up the database?
Who can find them the story
that was told this morning? Personal things on the
outside, but what he speaks of
are the external signs. If you want to bear fruit, first
names, special hat,
the external signs that you have
enormous refuge, and what he says, what is it
called?
The second husband, the escape of the
second husband, nobody knows.  That you
do that,
and who irritates me as a
second husband, he comes from me. There are
14 Diamond Mountain people, it
came from somewhere else.
He said, "I can't believe
everyone I address is so stupid. I
am surrounded by stupid people, and
all this longer here, they
understand it. They take the goods to
flee, and nobody knows if you took the
flight or not. You
understand the apprenticeship, and that's something very
quiet, and nobody can prove it. And people still come
to me
and say, 'I experienced the apprenticeship.
I have a healthy light grid. Do
n't forget a real Adriatic, and
preservation.' I believe you have
done
some of the qualities. If you
have directly experienced the majority, that
you are sure you have experienced it,
and if a high lama says, 'That's why you
haven't directly experienced the majority,'
then, 'Okay, you know for sure what
you have experienced.' If you have done it, then it
is done. If
you have done it, then you know it,
and you are sure. If the world
explodes, then you can't do anything about it.
That tells me  Something, I don't care
if you have to say it, then you have
n't experienced it.
and after that I promise you a
break, so at half past the meditation. 16
after the break he went through
the schedule again and in the end in the
instructions, keep group 1 meditation,
group 2 and we'll show them to
number 16.
Very helpful if you die,
to take refuge, it's the same if you
crash a plane,
if you just remember the name of your lama, the one at the
end through the red, the
white and black list, fata morgana,
the tidal wave, the mountains collapsing,
if, if, if you notice that the
standardized hallucinations
start, every HC who dies, beetles, fish,
people, if you notice that they start,
then start saying the name of your
lame, if not, then
I tried to assign the man to the 21st,
and if you can, just
say the name of your father,
if I were you, the lamb from the book,
then really called there,
only if the name of a lama is on your
lips  If you fall, then
you don't need to worry.
What does the question mean? What does it mean? Okay,
if you give my personal
opinion, 11, I believe that if you have a
good relationship with a heart teacher
and you say their name, then I
believe you cannot be reborn in the
middle realms.
But that's just my opinion. Okay, and what
happens if you think about it, but not as
far as you wish?
I would go to the lama's name and
try to find the majority there.
I've been in such situations,
to be honest. You can only
say your lama's name. The idea of ​​the
choir at the moment, if you're bothered that
you can suddenly erase a bad step every 65 years,
it's unlikely. I don't think it's
possible.
I don't think you can
change their habits at that moment.
You can, if you die, the 65
just built up long met in praise. That
means you don't put your cards on it now,
that Charlie is hallucinating.
It's like being in the middle of a nightmare.
You don't have the capacity and the
ability, so to speak, a few  Steps around
16, that's not how it's going to be, you couldn't do that,
so take care of it now,
real store means take care of it
now, understand that he has now while
your mind is still clear and don't
wait until the moment comes when
your mind is so confused, like never before
in my life, because you can, I remember,
I wanted some, I'll
tell you another story about a
person who went to Indonesia,
we might go, of course, such nearby,
if I
tell it here now, then at least I won't have anything left
to tell the girls.
[Music]
You can
listen to it later, okay, now pause,
we have to stay on topic, please, please, please, please, please, okay, go
home and I've found something for you,
I'm going to tell you the story of the
pearl lady touring,
the pearl ladies,
it's just his
story from back then and it has no connection,
but I think it's beautiful, where were we
shopping, we were in Taiwan in a
coffee house, that it's the third story,
how the wheel of life came about, to get to know
all the stories, we have to go on
to Indonesia.
My picture course was happily sent,
even the photo team responsible for it. They've finally
found the right section, and it took us several months,
but they've finally
found the right place.
I'll show you the photo. So,
we know where we have to go. We'll
climb up the mountain and
then explain the story of life from the
pictures.
This is another story. The
Water of Life was painted.
It contains the idea that if
your lama's name is on your lips, then
when you die, everything will be alright. That's it. It's
a negative story
that happened during life,
which required a new
rule to be made.
In the beginning, there were no rules
about not drinking alcohol,
and then there was no one defending themselves while drunk.
And when was a rule
made that you're not allowed to drink here?
These stories, these negative
stories, are called lengths, and here's
the one on the left.
This is the story for a
nun. It rules that they are not allowed to
argue with each other.
It comes from the nuns' vows, from the Viennese, from
the arrow.  I heard
what the longest is, not arguing or
was in a course,
that is a special kind of tree in
India,
the putter was very successful for
people, such direct experiences, the
teacher Hyde to lead in this park,
also the diamond cutter's mother was
spoken to in a park and then
these park lectures became very popular
and Butter gave lessons without ceasing at that time
and the king, so
Dana, that is where the father also came to
the lectures,
he simply became interested because of
his son's lectures,
he and his wife went to
the park to listen to them,
he started to dress warmly
and the people came like
bees to honey, the drama was as sweet
as honey and the people were and we didn't
have time to completely and the king,
he, the brother's father and all his
friends went home again in the evening after the lecture
and there was
a letter from the helper Jana and
I think it was one of the four
little tigers, one of the first students
of Buddha
Ettenheim and said  Always up, where has he
already heard it? It's
in this, in this homage to
Hradčany. It says we are so blessed,
and he went in and always says
up. This expression is
two and a half thousand years old. He said to
his wife, Emma, ​​up.
[Music]
I must have some good Kramer seeds
because the lectures were in this garden,
and his wife said, "Why do
you always say that?" What happened was emptied all day,
and thousands of
people had achieved the highest spiritual
results.
And then his wife said, "That's not
mine, but I don't have any good seeds.
We are not my good seeds."
And then it was on devices, and they
said, "Why do you have something like that?"
Because the mother came into the world to
teach men.
He didn't come here for the women,
and she was quite... And then
he said, "My... No, that you do
n't say
or want to help all living beings.
Why place, why organized? Why don't
you women get together and
organize a contract with Butter?" He
measured all beings, and that's why
all the women from the city map
met and said, "Let's
go and ask Butter."  Whether he
teaches us women, only women
allowed, and then the husband said,
why only women?
We feel intimidated in the presence of
men, we can't let our hair
down,
we can't behave naturally, we
only want women to be able to have
such a lecture.
Then she said, I have my suggestion:
four men go before lunch,
and we women then have it in the afternoon.
But he thought it was a good
idea, but he thought it was disrespectful.
If I ask the father of the
food, can we have a warm
afternoon because the king is
n't a woman? And then I thought it would be
appropriate if I asked the king's wife.
I think it's...
I don't think it's... the mother of
Nordphoto. At this point, I
still want to... the mother has already spoken, and
I think I'll ask her for permission,
and she can then convince the king,
and they did everything, and 500 women from
the city map went to the park,
and the women who went to the garden...
When I helped Lot's mother with a lecture,
we were already on pretzels when
we should  They looked beautiful, and all the
women had made themselves pretty, wearing silk
and jewels.
What the monks were allowed to do was stay.
The husbands of the Chargers had to
stay home. And then he
looked at the monks and saw the whole
charade. And then he
thought to himself that some of
these monks weren't advanced enough to
have such beautiful women around them. The
women are so beautiful.
[Music]
And then he said to the women, "
You shouldn't make yourselves beautiful when
he comes to give the lecture. It's really
not good for the young monks who are
n't experienced."
Quite frankly, his company
here isn't free from desire. And
the women understood immediately. They
took off their jewelry. And then there was
a young woman who was a servant
and overheard this. She could drown with her teeth,
and they
asked her to take the jewelry home.
[Music] "
Take home, please take our
jewelry home."
And then they took all the jewels
and jewelry, and he
went back to the village. And then he
started to learn. But there was a
young lady, a wife, and she was  Too
proud to find her pearls again, and she
's still wearing her pearls,
and/or teaching her, she's simply
distracted by her pearls.
She has no skill with pearls,
and then she shouldn't have been taught about
the meditation of dying through the media
so that she wouldn't
think about her pearls anymore.
And then he taught the meditation,
and she just keeps looking at her
pearls. Now she simply didn't listen, and the woman
who asked for your lecture
said to herself, "I have to make her stop
looking at her pearls.
I'll send the servant back
to the house to bring me my
big pearls, and I'll put
them on, and then she'll stop
looking at her cheap pearls, like in the old days." When I have really expensive ones,
she won't be distracted anymore. That's what
the Berliner woman said, but
I've changed my mind. Please
bring me my pearl.
By the way, if you're
interested, it wasn't a necklace
but a single piece. Motto: So if you, if
you, with your dreams, long dress, if
you offer, this little vest
that goes under the breast  stops and
that means his motto is this
made of pearls just said go back and
praise Mainz e motor if this girl
Mainz motors
then she will forget her pearls and
finally hear again
so she sent Nadine back
[Music]
the servant who went home it has
now thought about it always up
but this time it is an annoying
topic up everyone else is allowed to
hear back then I have to run around with the pearls being a
servant in these times in India
is not fair
it's really no fun paying a servant
everyone every day
I earn little and that's all
and that's honest in the past
no drama had heard and now
I have again inside no warmth
I will always stay like this I want to hear
the barmer and the brother did
he read the thoughts when she goes back
and then he saw that she will
not live long and then he
magically painted a
loser on a white tree trunk
as a birch before I gave paper
to her for it  To write, he used
this white bark of the skin, so she goes,
and he magically conjured a
verse from the previous day on this tree: all things that are born will
die.
You should understand your life.
You should try to plant good karma.
I'm giving you war now. I'm giving you
these private shows. The tree
trunk was full, and she is totally blind,
he says, and takes off the pieces of bark and
goes on to get the room there,
or wrote me my own poem.
I am really very
special and for herself. She kept reading the verse. They had read it aloud to each other,
and when did a cow warn them?
The cow struck at her,
and she died. And when, what does she do,
so simply, but she had mother's
name on her lips. That's why
we read this story. She
had the name of the food on her
lips when she took risks, when she was
struck, and how she died with mother's
name on her lips.
So, if you're interested, the cow
was pregnant. I don't know why they
say that,
and because she died with  Butt as a
name on her lips and that's why
she was reborn as a princess of Sri Lanka
and because she had the pearls in her hands
and the day she was born,
pearls from the sky had
rained from the sky
very early in Lanka, so her mother and
father then said maybe
we should take the pearl girl
and analyze the girl called
pearl and retailer came in
a boat, panic was perceiving a
boat off the coast of southwest India and there was
a strong storm and the boat
was driven to Sri Lanka and the
station street,
what is pregnant, that is true, warlord,
or when the Ammann tailor
spoke, they were quite by chance
from Schramma's table and then s  And they
landed so far and did their business.
We rented an apartment next to the king's palace,
and every AMG dealer
gathered, and together, loudly, something like that succeeds
again, drives like that, or
the soldier Schneider Sforza, and they sang, and I started
to go, and the girl was in the
palace and heard this beautiful,
beautiful song, such a
beautiful life, they are really good
musicians, and then a father
asked her to invite these elephant musicians to the
palace to sing for us. He has a
lot of money and asked the businessmen,
just emails, if it could be more of a rock 'n' roll band, could
you come to the palace and sing for us?
And then we said we
are not singers, businessmen know,
but we sing together every night,
the heart, and that the man was like that,
tried a prayer, and then left,
and then she asked what it was about,
and they said it was about what, and at
that moment, what happened to her,
or, and the memory from  In
fact, they got him to talk to
his brother about his past life, and then they
told him how Kohl was,
and then they told his whole
story, how he was enlightened in the present,
the whole
story, and at the end of the
evening she said, "When you're finished
and you're about to drive home, could he
visit me briefly? I'd like to send this guy
a message." And then
she wrote a message to Buddha,
and it's a poem: "
People and gods bow down before you, you
want, you are freed from
the fear of life and of being
reborn.
Can you give me nectar, the World Cup?
Can you give me the nectar of
immortality?" And then
they drove back to Schwabach and
handed him the message,
and where Wenning said, "If you ever come again after a
long drive, could you
please take a message with you?" "Yes, of
course we will," and
meanwhile, Lord Butter had
painted a portrait of himself, which she wanted him to
send, and at the bottom of the portrait, he
had painted the Wheel of Life. It's
a strange message for someone.
whom you don't know or have just met,
you have a portrait
with the wheel of life, and now he had
written the famous work,
and he wrote these two famous verses on it,
and received the message and
the painting, and opened up,
what is this, and then they explained what
this painting is about and who
is depicted in the painting, and they
went into her bedroom, and
then she recited the twelve songs three times,
and before she
came to the end the last time, she directly learned about the teachers,
and then she
spoke another leading poem,
you love far away, I don't know you,
but you
opened my eyes,
you are, you are the best physician in
this world,
you tore the false ideas about the world
from my mind,
I bow to the greatest physician,
and then she said, could this
go back to buttering, singing because
she has become Adrian,
and then she sent best wishes to
Lord Brother and instructions, having become a
teacher, I will never again be
drilled in the bright rooms,
I will never again be an animal, I  I
will never be a hungry ghost again.
I will never be human again. I
will never be the demigod.
I am free. The
ocean of blood and tears has
dried up.
I have crossed the mountain of skeletons.
I have crossed the mountain of false views.
With my [unclear], though destroyed, I have
become [unclear] thanks to you. I
crossed the ocean. I am crossing the ocean.
Now I will always take refuge.
Input Adama Untersander. And can you
ask him to give me the lay vows?
Can I have this beloved? And they
parked three packages of balls.
She really parked three beautiful boxes with
pearls and packed them for the
merchants. And she instructed the merchants to
put butter under
jewels. Her home comes for everyone a
chance, a box. And because they
come home, they all look the same.
There was brought and then the Lord
asked again.
Gladly, can you still remember the
unfortunate [unclear], the unfortunate
servant who was totally unhappy
asking the numbers back and forth?
Special construction was kicked, yes,
I can remember that I was
sad and had
my name on the
Luther when she died, that's why she was reborn as a princess
of slender and I sent
the prohibition of life,
and that's why she
directly experienced the majority and then said to
each other, hey, that's totally cool, that
makes me very happy,
what should I do now with the three
boxes of pearls, so the
box that she dedicated to the mother
is for me and I want you to
clip it to the wall of the temple so that
the temple becomes beautiful, Allplan, it can
do that with my pairs,
the box that is for the lady, jewels,
you have to give that to people who
practice the warmth and the box
that is for the St, the St,
and then,
and there were Munich ones who were
specialized in
giving lectures, and there were only moderately specialized ones in Vienna,
others in Abidjan,
and now guess what happened and
everyone showed me how the box stands,
so Diaby, there, boys, times,
how does it belong to us and the  Viennese people said, "And
stand by it," and the football boys said, "And
stand by it," and then
they argued with each other,
and that's the end of the story. And
where it says, "Argue and don't stride,"
physical going, monks and
nuns shouldn't
argue with each other.
That's the longest one. It's not about the council's
life, and not about the twelve
songs.
It's about not arguing, and that's why a
rule had to be made
that Munich calls itself not wanting to
rage.
Okay,
that's the short version.
I think it's Richie's
summary. I think there's a
200-page version so you can see
that it's the ten-page version. There's the
longer version, which is very, very nice,
200 pages long, very, very nice. That's
another lesson about the hair of
life in which it's explained.
Maybe we'll do it, or moderator
Dennie can do an attachment now.
I already have it on. Viewers must.
That's the forbidden retreat. At the moment, it
costs $1500,
so if you register now,
only in this class, you get
a special price.
I hope he all comes. Thank you.
[Music]
She learns they are free the money all hotel
and we picked a nice hotel
it's a five-star hotel and it's a
two-hour flight from Singapore and it works out
pretty well it's really
easy for you to get there said
Kater and then another connecting flight
this photo was taken two days ago
by our team in became
butter and this is one of the stories
and defenders could identify
about the wheel of life identify
we're really going up the mountain and I'm going to show
you the wheel of life from the
painting and we're doing the book with
a famous German photographer
Bernd Kohl his famous businessman
he was Entrepreneur of the Year
he founded the internet business in
Germany and we also did
a program together and
he's a very famous photographer as we
try to finish the book beforehand
but I don't know if I